[beeping]
Hey, so, where's Anzu?
#12 LAST STORY!?
[Hijiri] She should have been
out here by now.
Huh. I think she was in the break room
last time I saw her.
[suspenseful music]
[Anzu] What was that?
My head hurts. It feels…
[Anzu gasps]
Blood?
I gotta get out of here.
[Yukana] You're just like all the others…
always in my way.
-[door opens]
-[hurried footsteps]
[Arisa] Stop!
You're not going alone.
We should split up.
We'll cover more ground.
-Mm-hm.
-Yes.
[Tsuchiya] Mr. Hijiri,
allow me to handle this.
You should remain at work.
[door opens]
[Arisa pants]
What did you do, Anzu?
Without my magic, I'm useless to you.
[Arisa and Tsukasa panting]
[gasps]
[tense music]
[Tsukasa] Hoshino!
You came for me, my love.
[gasps]
Here.
[Tsukasa grunts in pain]
Hm.
[Yukana] Tsukasa…
[breathing heavily]
I understand. Everyone else is in the way.
None of this is any of your fault.
[gasps]
[Anzu] I would have believed you
even when nobody else did.
How dare you! Get away from Hoshino!
-[slaps]
-[knife clangs]
[Tsukasa exhales heavily]
[Yukana] Tsukasa? But why, my love?
Sh-- Shut up! I am not your love!
Everything you put me through!
And now you go after her!
I never wanna see your face
or hear your voice ever again!
Do you understand me?
Get out of my sight!
[Yukana] There's no need
for such silly lies.
[Tsukasa gasps]
I understand.
No one else will understand you like I do.
My sweet Tsukasa,
I'll love you every minute of every day
for the rest of my life.
[moans]
[Yukana] The sweet boy I know
wouldn't resort to this kind of violence.
I see now. I need to stay by your side.
You have some bad influences.
Hmm?
We make this perfectly clear.
If you keep trying to get to Kazuki,
you're gonna have to go through me first,
because I will always be right here
by his side!
I will never let you get near him,
no matter what!
[siren wailing]
[Anzu groans]
[officer] Are you the one who called?
[Arisa] Yes! That woman is armed
and is extremely dangerous!
-[officer] Call it in! We need an…
-Hey, hey! Hold on!
[siren fading]
TRAFFIC SAFETY PROGRAM NOW ENFORCED
[approaching footsteps]
[gasps]
You're okay.
Hey, guys!
You didn't all need to wait for me.
Anzu, are you all right?
Yeah, turns out
it was just a little scratch.
-Mm. That's a relief.
-[Saki] That's a relief.
[chuckles]
[Tsukasa's dad] Tsukasa.
-[Tsukasa's dad clears throat]
-[Tsukasa] Dad, Mom.
Are you Anzu Hoshino?
[Anzu] Yes.
It's my son's fault.
I'm sorry you were involved.
Please accept our sincerest apology.
[breathing nervously]
[grunting]
[Tsukasa groans in pain]
Ow, uh…
[Tsukasa's dad] We're all truly sorry.
I understand your parents are out of town.
I would like to apologize
to them as well when they return.
For now, you'll have to excuse us.
[groans]
-[Tsukasa's dad] We're leaving.
-[Tsukasa grunts]
Huh? Uh…
[Tsukasa's dad exclaims]
[Anzu] Let's go home, Kazuki.
[grunts]
Hey!
Tsukasa needed your support tonight.
But just like before,
you blamed him for everything.
Do you know how hurtful that is?
Aren't you his father?
Of all people, I'd think
you would be the one stepping up
to protect him!
Let's go.
[grunts]
[Junta] She's right. We should go.
[groans]
How dare she.
Such disrespectful behavior!
[Arisa laughing]
Stop laughing!
[Tsukasa's mom] Mm, uh…
[Anzu] I told you, Mom, I'm totally fine.
But I can use more cute pics of Momohiki.
Good night.
[door opens]
Mm. So, guess what?
My mom's coming back home.
I tried to tell her
there was nothing to worry about,
but she insisted.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Hoshino, how is it
that you were always saving me?
Huh, I am?
You are.
[soft piano music]
[phone chimes]
[Ayami] Hey, Tsukasa, how you've been?
Did you hear about
the junior high reunion?
You'd better come.
It's been way too long, I miss you.
[girl 1] Where you've been lately?
I miss you.
[girl 2] So, got a girlfriend yet?
[girl 3] Tsukasa, it's me.
[gags]
-Ah…
-Oh…
[phone clatters]
[yelps]
I'm so sorry!
[Tsukasa sighs]
That's a pretty good crack.
I'm so sorry.
Please, let me pay to fix it.
[Tsukasa] You don't have to pay
for the repairs.
Well, then, thanks. Thanks a lot!
I'm sorry, uh, I bumped you! Goodbye!
[Anzu wailing]
Uh…
[chuckles softly]
[Anzu grunting]
Huh?
[eerie chuckle]
Uh, hey, are you okay?
-[sighs]
-[Makoto] Come on, don't just stand there,
-help her up!
-All good! I'm totally fine!
[doors clank]
[both] One set A.
-Huh?
-Um…
[Anzu groans]
-Hey.
-[shrieks]
[Tsukasa] I get the feeling
she's gonna be just fine.
SHUKAN HIGH INDUCTION CEREMONY
Hey! Better hurry, Kazuki's leaving.
He's too fast. I gotta catch up with him!
[Tsukasa] I'd better go straight home.
-[Rena] Kazuki!
-[Tsukasa] Please just stop.
Leave me alone.
-[thuds]
-[Anzu] Whoa! Sorry!
-[Tsukasa] Huh?
-[Rena] Oh hey, watch out.
-My bad, sorry! In a hurry!
-Uh?
Hey, Kazuki!
[Tsukasa] From the first time
you caught my eye…
Out of respect for my friend,
I can't help.
Thanks for inviting me along.
-[Tsukasa] You've always…
-But you've been a real lifesaver for me.
[Tsukasa] …known exactly
the right thing to say.
You're always saving me.
[phone chimes]
[Anzu] Huh? Yes!
Mom just sent a ton of Momohiki pics!
[squeals]
[Anzu chuckles]
Mwah!
Stop me if you hate this.
[Anzu] Uh…
[Tsukasa] Somewhere along the way,
you became really important to me.
[Tsukasa] Thank you.
[Anzu sighs]
[Anzu] But of course!
What are friends for?
[tender music]
[sighs]
[yawns]
I'm so thirsty.
Didn't know you were up.
[door squeaks]
-[thuds]
-[Junta groans]
[sobs]
Sorry, I interrupted!
It's not like that!
[Miyoko] My little Anzu!
I know you don't always act like it,
but you are a girl.
You can't afford to have
a scar on your face.
Now it's gonna be even harder for you
to attract your soulmate.
-[Anzu] Mom, stop it.
-[whines]
[Arisa] There's no need
to worry about that.
A true soulmate can see past your scars.
Besides, she practically proposed
to Tsukasa already.
Arisa!
I will always be at his side!
Ooh!
You've got the wrong idea!
I didn't mean it like that!
Speaking of boys, where's Junta?
[Anzu] Baseball practice.
[Miyoko] I haven't seen him in a while.
I was looking forward to catching up.
Well, speaking of catching up,
did Dad come too?
[Miyoko] Someone has to stay and take care
of Momohiki. He drew the short straw.
You just left him, huh?
I'm really curious.
How will they punish her?
The authorities need to do something.
This whole situation
has become such a nightmare.
[Arisa] It's just so concerning
because I know how persistent
that girl has always been in the past.
What do you mean you can't cover
for her anymore?
What are we supposed to do?
[Yukana's uncle]
I've said all I can about it.
-[hangs up]
-[Yukana's mom] Wait! Hello?
[sighs]
[Yukana's uncle] Again, I'm terribly sorry
for the trouble my niece has caused.
It's fine.
However, if she attempts
to hurt my friends again…
Do we understand each other?
[suspenseful music]
[Riri] Attaboy, Hijiri.
Way to go, putting
those family connections to good use.
I was counting on you.
Unfortunately, I don't think
this punishment is gonna cut it.
[water plops]
[Yukana] Separated from my love
once again.
But do not fear, my sweet.
We are destined to be together.
I am the only one who can save you
from all those people,
who want to keep us apart.
-[Riri] Good evening.
-[gasps]
Huh?
Who are you?
Well, hey there! The name's Riri.
I'm a wizard.
Sadly, my wand's been
out of order for a bit,
and I haven't been able to use my magic.
Are you crazy?
That's funny.
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
[ominous music]
[gasps in fear]
[Anzu] It's kinda strange. I haven't heard
a peep from Riri since the incident.
At last!
[mumbling]
It's finally happening. You missed me.
No! Did not!
What do you want anyway?
[Riri] I know you called.
My Anzu senses were tingling.
[giggles]
[sighs]
[Rio] Oh, I get it.
You were hoping to get to see…
this version of me, huh?
-I didn't call!
-[yelps]
And no matter what form you're in,
you still look like
the world's biggest piece of crap!
Such flowery language!
I just came to tell you
you don't have anything to worry about.
Your troubles have all vanished!
Now you can just focus on being you.
And don't ever change, okay?
I love you.
[kisses]
-[Anzu] You bastard! Get over here!
-[Rio yelps]
[Rio] That was close! Here you go!
[Anzu huffs]
[chuckles]
Well, that was fun, but I gotta go!
Goodbye, Anzu.
Wait! What the heck was that about?
[birds chirping]
[Anzu] What? She lost her memory?
Yeah, at least
that's what her lawyer said.
Kishi seems to have suffered
some sort of break,
resulting in a loss of memory.
She can't remember anything
from the past few years,
including Tsukasa.
Are they sure this girl isn't lying?
[Arisa] The doctors seem to believe
it's the truth.
Well, that's good news, then.
You should be relieved.
You can finally go back
to living your life without fear.
I guess. It's so sudden,
it doesn't feel real yet.
[Anzu] Take all the time you need
to process it.
Huh?
[soft chuckle]
Yeah.
Anzu!
-Dad! You're here!
-Ah! You're here!
[Anzu's dad] I was worried about you,
I couldn't stay away
while I knew my little girl
was going through such a rough time.
Plus, check out all these sweet gifts
I brought back
just for you to help cheer you up!
[Anzu] Games and chocolate!
[pig snorts]
And don't forget the special pork buns.
Pork buns? Hold on,
weren't they relocated to the US?
-[Anzu's dad] And last but not least…
-[meows]
[Anzu] Momohiki!
Momohiki! Momohiki! Momohiki!
[smooches, exclaims]
-Missed you so much!
-[meows]
[Anzu] Hey.
Games, chocolate, and my Momohiki?
My three greatest desires,
all suddenly back at once?
What the heck does this mean?
[insects chirruping]
[Anzu] Don't you wanna sleep
in the office with Dad?
He snores so loudly after traveling.
Oh.
[snoring loudly]
Maybe I should just go home.
Why? Her mom said you could stay, right?
Yeah, but I don't wanna sleep
in the same room as you.
Wow, way to sugarcoat it.
-[Tsukasa] Hey.
-Huh?
[Tsukasa] I have to be honest
with you about something.
You know, uh, how I said before
that I didn't like Anzu in that way.
Well, things have changed.
What I'm trying to say--
-[Junta] I know, all right?
-[gasps]
[Tsukasa] What?
[Junta] Anzu's always been
one of the coolest people I know,
so I can see how you'd fall for her.
[Tsukasa] So, you're okay with it?
Oh, wait! That means that…
[sighs]
[Junta] …now I have to worry
about competing with you.
Not only that, but Ryuya as well.
Man, you do really have
low self-esteem, don't you?
You shouldn't worry too much.
I only just started feeling comfortable
around her.
Plus, she only thinks of me as a friend.
Huh?
What? Pretty sure
you're in the friend zone too.
Hey! You don't have to rub it in!
Whatever. I only told you
'cause we're housemates.
Feels weird sharing this kind of stuff.
Let's never talk about it again.
It's fine by me.
[soft chuckle]
Hmm.
[Anzu] I'm not sleepy at all,
so I'm just gonna go downstairs.
[Tsukasa] I'm not tired.
I think I'll go downstairs too.
Huh? No way. How is that fair?
Wait up, I'm coming too.
You've got practice
in the morning, remember?
[Junta] There's no way
I'm leaving the two of you alone.
I still cry just thinking
about the last time
when you got to hug her!
[whines]
[Tsukasa] Pull yourself together.
Riri, explain yourself!
Get out here, right now!
-[Kate] I'm afraid that Riri's not coming.
-What?
[Anzu] And, you are…
Sorry to show up out of the blue.
My name's Kate and I'm a wizard.
I'm sort of the new wizard in charge.
New wizard in charge?
'Fraid so, since Riri's not allowed
in the human world.
[Anzu] They're not?
-[Junta] Anzu?
-Huh?
-[Kate] Uh?
-[Junta gasps]
[Junta screams]
What's that?
-What's with the floating doll?
-[grumbles]
Wait, can you guys see that thing too?
[both] Mm-hm.
-What is this, furball?
-[Kate] My name's Kate.
I don't care what your name is!
Your magic's busted, fix it!
Not again! I blew it!
I forgot to use an illusion spell!
You're useless, you know that!
Cut me a little slack, will ya?
[groans]
This whole day has been
pretty hectic for me too!
-It's talking…
[playful music]
[Tsukasa] I don't know.
That story's pretty far-fetched,
even with the wizard
sitting right there in front of me.
Although when I think about it,
it actually explains a lot.
PIERCING BRANCH
SOAKING-WET ROOM
So, then, our reunion
was sped up to fit its timeline?
Man, how did I not notice
something like that?
I'm really sorry, you guys. I didn't mean
for you to get mixed up in this.
It's so embarrassing to be
subject number one for this stupid thing.
You've got nothing to apologize for.
I'm sure this has been hardest on you.
Besides, meeting you is what saved me.
So please don't apologize.
[Junta] I feel the same.
I don't care how.
I'm just glad we're reunited.
Junta, Kazuki.
Though, I really don't like
the idea of a forced romance.
Don't blame me. Both Riri and I
are just cogs in the corporate machine,
just following orders.
[gasps]
Hang on.
[Anzu] What do you mean,
they can't come back to this world?
Riri broke the rules and used taboo magic.
[Tsukasa] Taboo?
[Kate] 'Fraid so. They use
their magic to erase the memories
of Kazuki's stalker
for their own personal reasons.
But why? Why'd they do that?
Anzu's fault! The higher-ups thought
Riri developed feelings for Anzu
that went beyond the professional bounds.
[Kate] Remember when you were
attacked by those two men in the alley?
All of your friends
just randomly showed up.
[Anzu] Right, everyone arrived
after receiving those texts.
That interference was Riri's first strike.
They really crossed the line.
You see, we have very strict rules
about using our magic.
It must be used only for the development
of romantic relationships.
[Anzu] So, what's going to happen to Riri?
[Kate] Capital punishment
of the magic world.
[Anzu, Tsukasa and Junta] What?
It's usually what would happen,
but not this time.
The company was lenient,
and instead, settled for a life sentence
of cleaning the basement.
Life sentence?
I see. So they didn't want anyone
to know about Riri's actions.
Avoid the scandal.
[Kate] Of course.
The company has a reputation to maintain.
They'd agree on almost anything.
That's how Riri was able
to negotiate getting you back
your three greatest desires
as part of their deal.
Any more questions?
[Anzu] Nope, I think I understand
everything. Thanks for the insight, Kate.
Of course. I look forward
to working with you--
[Anzu grunts]
[action music]
[screams]
[Kate] Hey, wait! Oh…
What do you think you're doing?
Give me back my wand!
You're gonna let me see Riri right now.
If I remember correctly,
you can't use your magic
if your wand is contaminated.
[Kate] You wouldn't…
[Anzu] Imagine the trouble you'll be in
when your bosses find out
that on your first day,
you exposed yourself to humans,
and reveal the details
of your secret mission.
Add to that, wand contamination.
And just so you know,
my dad's been in here tonight,
and it wasn't pretty!
[whimpers]
[button clicks]
Your little stunt cost me my bonus.
My bosses agreed to 15 minutes
with Riri now.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah, no kidding.
That's how you play hardball.
[Kate] Stand back. I'm gonna summon Riri.
-[magical chimes]
-Go! Roma-roma! Kira-kira!
-[thuds]
-[groans]
-[slaps]
-[Riri groans]
Kate! Do you have to be so rough?
[whimpers]
Sorry.
-[Anzu] Riri.
-[gasps, chuckles]
[Riri] Anzu!
Could you transform for me?
What, what is it?
[sighs in relief]
That's much better.
-How dare you disappear on me like that?
-Stop, stop!
-Let go!
-[growls]
[Rio] You may not like it,
but everything Kate told you is true.
This is goodbye forever. After this,
I'll never be allowed to see you again.
But hey, you'll be fine. I mean,
I was only in your way, right, Anzu?
So…
[Rio sobs]
[Anzu] Thank you.
[gasps]
Seriously, you left
before I could say it, moron.
I'm sure an ordinary heroine
would have said that with more poise.
Too bad for you,
I'll always be an Anti-Heroine.
[Tsukasa] You know,
she's not the only one.
Thank you, Rio.
Kazuki, no. You and Anzu,
you guys shouldn't thank me for anything.
I messed up.
I broke the rules and ruined everything.
And now that you've got
your three greatest desires back,
you can just forget about me,
like a bad dream.
Are you dense?
That's nuts! Do you really think
I'd choose things over my friends?
Never! I would never forget about you.
So what is it you want?
Huh?
[Anzu] I'm asking you, Riri,
what do you want to do?
[Rio] Uh…
Anzu, what I want…
[Rio sobs]
…is to be…
here by your side!
[soft chuckle]
Then stay with me. It's that easy.
[tender music]
[Rio] Okay.
Oh, Anzu!
[cries]
[crying continues]
[Kate] So, hey, um,
are you guys almost done here?
'Cause we really need to wrap this up.
Hey, Furball! Read the room!
[Kate] I told you I'm Kate, not Furball!
Whatever!
Besides, Riri's not going anywhere.
Use your magic so they can stay for good.
I can't do that!
Like I said, magic can only be used…
[both] …if it contributes
to any romantic relationships!
That's right. Finally, she gets it.
[Anzu] Well.
What if I told you there's
a 0.00001 percent chance
that I'd fall for Rio,
making him my potential mate?
Rio? Wait! Oh…
[Junta and Tsukasa] Anzu?
As the wizard in charge,
you're making sure that I fall in love.
You can't separate me
from a potential mate.
-That'll break some rules, right?
-[Rio groans]
-[Anzu] Therefore…
-[whimpers]
It's completely and totally legal for you
to use your magic to keep Rio here!
-Wow.
-Whoa.
What?
Okay, fine then.
This is bad. I'm gonna get
such a pay cut for this.
-You really are the queen of debate!
-[chuckles mischievously]
[Anzu] Huh. Don't go getting
the wrong idea or anything.
I'm not cooperating with your project
and I'm not losing this game.
[gasps]
Neither am I.
I won't lose! Bring it on!
[Anzu] Once things calmed down,
my parents left again to go back to work.
[yawns]
I'm sleepy.
I was up way too late playing games.
[Anzu] And the three of us
continued living together.
The boss was nearly impossible to beat.
Don't fall asleep. You'll trip.
[Anzu] Yeah, yeah.
[Junta] Leave it to Anzu
to sleepwalk to school.
Huh?
[Hijiri] Good morning, my fellow students.
The new semester begins.
It must be a treat for you three
to get to be in my presence daily.
Huh?
We're just so grateful. You're a delight.
By the way,
thanks for pulling some strings.
-Now Kishi's family will stop--
-Who told you that?
Tsuchiya.
Mm-mm. Mm-mm. Mm-mm. Mm-mm…
[Anzu] It's admirable to do
such a good deed without showing off.
I-- I don't care
what you plebs think of me.
Again with this hot and cold act?
I don't know
if I've said this before, but,
I really appreciate our time together
on these walks to school.
What?
Uh, wait, did that sound weird?
Not at all. It's very sweet.
-[chuckles awkwardly]
-[Tsukasa] Could he be any more obvious?
[Anzu] I suppose I don't have
to actively avoid romance anymore,
since I did get
all of my things back, right?
-[Riri] Good morning!
-Huh?
-[Riri laughs happily]
-[Anzu] What? She's back?
[Anzu groans]
I'm here to tell you about the new rules.
The new rules?
Yep! You see, your games, chocolate,
and cat may have been returned for now,
but, unless you start prioritizing
romantic relationships,
you'll lose them all again!
Not fair! It's like facing the final boss
with level one weapon.
That's bad, right?
And if you finish high school
and you're still alone,
well, then they'll be confiscated forever!
[growls]
What?
I told you before,
I will not be forced into a relationship!
You'll see! I will not lose,
I'll win this project!
Ah! Anzu, you're so bold, I love it!
And let's not forget, you two,
that there's still a possibility
that Anzu ends up with me!
[giggles]
So, don't take it personally, okay?
You've done good but my kiss
is hard to compete with,
plus we've already kissed twice.
[in deep voice]
Do something about your mouth,
-or I will.
-[babbling]
Oh! Right here in front of everyone?
Are you sure?
[Anzu] Knock it off! You know what I mean!
[Riri] You're blushing!
Are you embarrassed?
[Anzu] I'm not blushing!
MEDICAL CENTER
My next subject
should be around here somewhere.
-[wand beeping]
-Oh, there she is.
[Kate] Hopefully
she's not as difficult to work with.
[theme music]
[Riri] Anzu's wonderful
and oh, so romantic developments
are slowly progressing as we speak.
[chuckles]